<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: growth | My Progressing Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://michaelpassion.github.io/blog/categories/growth/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://michaelpassion.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-09-11T12:02:25+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://michaelpassion.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Michael]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[carter1373043@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Don't Have Time]]></title>
    <link href="http://michaelpassion.github.io/blog/2014/08/29/i-dont-have-time/"/>
    <updated>2014-08-29T10:16:11+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://michaelpassion.github.io/blog/2014/08/29/i-dont-have-time</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>Is there something you&rsquo;d like to create? A project you want to build? A goal you want to achieve?</p></blockquote>

<!--more-->


<p><a href="http://www.mdswanson.com/blog/2012/10/28/i-dont-have-time.html">Original Link</a></p>

<hr />

<p>Is there something you&rsquo;d like to create? A project you want to build? A goal you want to achieve?</p>

<p>With the likes of <a href="http://www.gladwell.com/outliers/outliers_excerpt1.html">Malcolm Gladwell</a> and <a href="http://norvig.com/21-days.html">Peter Norvig</a> telling us that it takes
thousands of hours and many years to master something, your dreams and ambitions can
easily stall as reality sinks in.</p>

<p>How do you get the inertia to start when the finish line seems so far away?</p>

<blockquote><p>I&rsquo;d like to write a book, but I don&rsquo;t have time to do all that work.</p></blockquote>

<p>But do you have an hour to outline a table of contents? Could you write 500
words today? How about emailing five bloggers that might be interested in reviewing your
book this week?</p>

<p><a href="http://nathanbarry.com/">Nathan Barry</a>, a normal guy from Idaho with a wife and kid, found the time to write
his book in <a href="http://nathanbarry.com/commitment-changed-career/">thousand word chunks</a>.</p>

<blockquote><p>I&rsquo;d really like to start drawing, but I&rsquo;m no good and don&rsquo;t have time to learn.</p></blockquote>

<p>Do you have time to draw one sketch today? And again tomorrow? Could you steal enough
time to read a chapter in a <a href="http://www.drawright.com/">book</a> every week? To visit an art museum once a month?</p>

<p><a href="http://www.jonathanhardesty.com/">Jonathan Hardesty</a>, an aspiring artist who started at &ldquo;rock bottom&rdquo;, did
one sketch or painting <a href="http://conceptart.org/forums/showthread.php?870">every day</a>. It took him years of work, but he went
from untrained to professional artist.</p>

<blockquote><p>I love documentaries and want to make my own someday, but I don&rsquo;t think I&rsquo;ll ever find the time.</p></blockquote>

<p>Can you send an email to a subject you want to interview today? Could you edit just one
interview this week? Do you have a free weekend to film B-roll next month?</p>

<p><a href="http://timcawley.blogspot.com/">Tim Cawley</a>, with a day job in advertising, squeezed in work on nights, early
mornings, and holiday breaks for two years to complete <a href="http://fromnothingsomething.com/">his documentary</a>. It&rsquo;s now
showing at film festivals across the country.</p>

<hr />

<p>Gradual progress is crazy powerful.</p>

<p>When you frame something as a giant, amorphous task (get healthy, become a designer,
start a business) &mdash; it can seem impossible to fit into your busy schedule.</p>

<p>Break it down into smaller pieces that you do have time for.</p>

<p>With time and determination, the <strong>impossible</strong> will become the <strong>inevitable</strong>.</p>

<hr />

<p>总是觉得自己心比天高，命比纸薄。想学好多东西，也总有无从下手，觉得自己既没有天分，又下不了决心。其实是不够勇敢，执行力不够，再加拖延。正如文章所述：循序渐进的力量异常强大。当你规划某些庞大，杂乱无杂的计划时，你根本不可能将这些事加入你的“满满”的时间表中。但是如果你将他们分解，细化成你可以抽时间去做的小任务，再加上一点点时间和不放弃的决心，<strong>不可能</strong>就会成为<strong>必然</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
